Guide to the Records of the Office of Library Administration RG.38.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series III: Budget and Planning, 1966-1983
  - Budget, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Budget Allocation, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Budget Bobst Library, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Budget Estimate Worksheet, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Budget Estimate Worksheets, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Budget Estimation Worksheet, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Budget Planning, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Budget- Summary Data, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Budget Worksheets, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Budget Worksheets, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Building Equipment, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Building Purchase, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Carpet, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Coles, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Consortium Budget/Contract-New School (and Parsons), Cooper Union, NYU, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Construction Costs, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Construction Specifications, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Construction Specifications, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Contracts and Accounting, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cooper Union: Direct Payments For Local Books and Periodicals, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Copying, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Copying Machines, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cost Allocation, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Cost Allocation, 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Cost Allocation, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Cost Allocation Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Cost Allocation Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Cost Allocations, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Cost Allocations, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Cost Allocations, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Cost Allocations Committee, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - DA Budget- Construction, Equipment and Furniture, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Damage (Installation), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Date File, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Diesel Construction, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Dental School Library Worksheets, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Dormitory Authority, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Dormitory Authority, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Dormitory Authority, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Dormitory Authority, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Electrical Contractors, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Encumbrance Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Endowments, Special Funds, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - EPK Agenda (G.W.S.), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Equipment Requests, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Expenditure Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Final Sheets (Approved), 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Financial Info., 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Floor Plans- Bobst March 1976 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Foster- Architects, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - GBA Worksheets, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - General Accounting, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - General Financial and Budgetry Data, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - General Surveys, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Graphics, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Gunlocke Deliveries, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Hauserman Company, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Hauserman- Cut Outs, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - I7A Worksheets, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Internal Audit Department Report- Bobst LIbrary, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Invoices/Summary Detail, 1976-1979 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - LF Budget Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Library Book Budget, 1978-1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Library Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Library Consortium, 1975-1978 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Library Equipment, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Library Furnishings, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Library Furnishings- moving, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Locks and Keys, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Mandatory Retirement, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Media, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Memos, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mezzanine, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Music Listening, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - NYU Undergraduate Student Recruitment Marketing Plan, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - OMNI Cards, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Operating Budget, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Part-Time/Student Employment, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Penkaty Contractor, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Phone Systems, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Purchasing, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Reference, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Room Divider, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Russian Library, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Space, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Space (a), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Staff Development, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Student Projections Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Summary Budgets, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Summary Estimate, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Summary of Expense, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Summary of Expense- Budget Estimate Worksheet, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Summary of Recommendations As Taken From the Text of The Report (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Tabulation, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Tamiment, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Tannenbaum, Arthur, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Turnstiles, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - University Senate Meeting December 11, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Working Data, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 44)